A full calendar of energy events throughout the year.
In March, we discussed annual energy stamps and durables at the EWT71 in Nanshan.
EWT stands for Energy Working Group in APAC.
In April, the 37th APAC Expert Group on Energy Data and Analysis in Guangzhou
and so explore how energy data can support the development and security of energy.
In May, the EWG reported to the senior officials at the SOM2 in Shanghai,
that's the senior official meeting in the diplomatic track.
In June, we addressed the next generation power system challenges at a symposium in Hangzhou,
And just last month, we exchanged practices on the destructive energy and AI implications in Shenzhen for the 67th APAC expert group meeting on energy efficiency and conservation.
After our gathering in Fuzhou for this training program coming up in late August,
There are four Semitic Energy Site events in SOM3 in Dalian, which covers Zero-carbon
industrial parks, CCUS, Think-time Dialog, and AI energy integration.
And finally, the harvest season for our energy track this year, the APAC Baiting Energy Week
in the middle of September, for the final deliveries and the outcomes.
The Beijing Energy Week, composed with the APAC Energy Ministerial Meetings, the EWG 72, and a series of side events.
So we welcome and invite all of you to join us, to share ideas, to explore partnerships, and to build on the issue of saving the energy community for all together.
In closing, I wish this program every success and wish all of you have a productive and
enjoyable stay in Fuzhou.
Thank you very much.